Beal, Edwin F., Papers /3056
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edwin F. Beal Papers
1945-1952
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Beal, Edwin F.
/3056
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
"Origins of Co-determination in West Germany." This was a research study done by Mr. Beal in Germany in 1951 and accepted as a Ph.D. Thesis. The thesis is cataloged, HD5660 G3 B36. Published material dealing with the German economy, of a general nature was sent to the University Library.
8436528
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of pamphlets, releases, and other materials from companies, unions and the U.S. Office of the High Commissioner.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4085: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers
Beal, Edwin Fletcher
8436528
- A Decade of American Foreign Policy, 1941-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Gross Britannien (Box 1, Folder 2)
  German, Bound
- Danemark (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Das Bayerische Betriebdrategesetz, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Report on Germany, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Landesverfassung Der Freien Hansestadt Bremen, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Furund wider, 1919-1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Weissbuch, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Bound, German
- Report on Germany, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Report on Germany, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Mitbestimmungsrecht und Arbeitsrecht, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Nachtrag zum Material Zur Aufteilunf Der, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  German, bound
- Deutschen Gerwerkschaftsbundes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Die Entflechtung und Neuordnung der Eisen Schaffenden Industrie, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Report on Germany Jan. 1- Mar. 31, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Report on Germany April 1- June 30, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Deutschland (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Dueck Ripperdey Dietz, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Gleicher Lohn der Frau fur gleiche Leistung, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- DAG, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  bound, German
- DAG, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Frauen und Mitbestimmung, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Wirtschaftskammer-Gesetz, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Deutsche Betriebspsychologie, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Walter Ulbricht, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Auslandsschriften Des DGB - Italien (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Osterreich, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Report on Germany July 1 - Sept. 30 1951 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Gesetz 75 Und Ruhrstatut, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Die Wirtschaftsstruktur der Sowjetzone, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Gewerkschaften Und Schlichtungswesen, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Die Neuordnung der Grundstoffindustrien, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Report on Germany April 1-June 30, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Germany The Story in Documents, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Military Government of Germany, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Military Government of Germany, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Norwegian (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Germany 1947-1949 The Story in Documents (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bayerisches Betriebdrategesetz, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Tarif-Vertrag (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Der Christliche Gedanke in Der Wirtschaft, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Military Government of Germany Public Health and Medical Affairs, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Labor - Office of Military Government for Germany, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Industrial Demilitarization, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Bizonal Level of Industry Plan, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Progress of German Preparations, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Socialization in the Soviet Zone, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Military Government of Germany, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Military Government of Germany, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Military Government of Germany, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- The Evolution of Bizonal Organization, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Lohntarifvertrag, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Warum Mitbestimmung in der Wirtschatt, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Die Internationale Gewerkschaftsbewegung, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- USA (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Schweden (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Die Gewerkschats Bewegung in Deutschland, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Tarif-Vertrag Schlosser- und Maschinenbauer-Innung Bremen (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Hammer Oder Amboss, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- DGB Der Tarifvertrag, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Hesse - A New German State, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Manpower Policy in Western Germany, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Special Report on German Labor Front; Misc. German Language Articles, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Chapter 1 - The Initial Aims of the Occupation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  German
- Bremen (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Development of German Labor Law, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- German Language Articles, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Und Die Deutschen Gewerkschaften, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- German Language Articles (Box 2, Folder 8)
- German Language Articles; Booklets, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- FDGB, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- FDGB (Free German Trade Union Association), 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Sex Differentials in Wages and Salaries, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Berlin Sector, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- German Booklets, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)